Ameer Abdrabo

9430 Dundee Place, Tinley Park, 60487, United States, (708)-737-4997, ameerabdrabo7@gmail.com

LINKS	<u>Linkedin</u>	
PROFILE	I am a dynamic individual who has conquered numerous roles and amassed a wealth of experience. I have an impressive track record of achievements, including an increase of profit every year I worked at Charleys Philly Steaks as a manager. I have exceptional qualities including a strong work ethic, problem solving skills, leadership abilities, time management and excellent customer satisfaction.	
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY		
May 2016 — Jul 2020	Manager, Charleys Philly Steaks	Lansing
	 Supervised, trained, advised, and assisted Created weekly schedules. Checked inventory weekly and placed or Monitored compliance with sanitation as Boosted online rating by 50% Increased sales yearly by 20%. 	ders.
Aug 2020 — Present	Service Agent, Enterprise Orland Hills	
	 Organized and managed lot cleanliness. Updated inventory and prices. Helped customers better understand the features of the vehicles. Ensured that the vehicles were in great condition and ready for sale. Assisted in group record for cars sold in a month. 	
EDUCATION		
Aug 2018 — Dec 2022	Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering, University of Illinois at Chicago	
	Honors:	
	• Deans List	
	Relative Course Work:	
	 Data Structures, Logic Design, Embedded Systems, Electronics, Advanced Circuit Anaylsis, Computer Organization, Digital Systems Design, Digital Signal Processing, Computer Architecture, VLSI Design 	
SKILLS	Leadership and Management Skills	Ability to Work in a Team
		Time Management
	Multitasking	Bilingual (English & Arabic)
	Excellent Customer Service	
HOBBIES	Sports and Fitness Volunteer Work Reading	